Good morning. My name is Mie Fujitani.
Today I would like to introduce our pre-live routine at Illibeen's.
We enter the dressing room as carnivores.
Once in the dressing room, I become a herbivore to switch over.
First.
Warm up with the four-legged stomp.
In both live performances and sumo wrestling, it is important to get into the right stance. On the day of a live performance, I always eat Ken Yamagata's cherries in the dressing room.
Eating them makes a difference in the moisture in my throat.
Cherry charge is complete!
Next time I will eat Ken Yamagata's cherries.
Health by reference!
I would like to make up!
Yamagata Genjin also makes cherry blossoms for lip!
My recent favorite is sugar cane!
Cherry charge complete!
I will look for my destiny!
I've been doing this for about 5 years now, but I can't seem to find it!
Continuation is power!
Health by reference
The time for the live is approaching
I'm going to eat a mysterious fruit that makes me excited.
Five mystery berries cost 128,000 yen!
I highly recommend them and hope everyone will try them!
I'll put it in the summary section.
This is Miyu Fujitani's backstage routine.
See you later.
Good morning. My name is Hikaru Natsuki.
Today I would like to show you my pre-live routine at E-WINDS.
I'm a little embarrassed, but I'll show you something special.
Ta-da! I'd like to set up my hair.
I'm going to brush it and make my hair cuticles shiny.
I usually wear my hair in twin-tails.
Today, I'm thinking of braiding my hair for the first time in a while.
Now that my hair is done, I'd like to have a meal next.
On the day of the concert, I need to eat well to be able to move, so I want to eat a lot!
Today's menu is carrots and cabbage.Today's menu is carrots and cabbage.
I always try to chew a lot because it makes me feel full with a small amount of food!
I chew a lot!
Okay, now that we've finished eating and we're full, I'd like to say a few words.
I would like to say out loud.
Mmm-hmm
I'm Hikaru Tsuki.
Mmm.
Mmm-hmm.
This is Hikaru Tsukihi.
Okay.
Well, I'd like to do it like this
To calm my mind before the concert
I'd like to watch some animal healing videos.
Wow, what cute animals!
Wow, they're eating a lot of food.
So cute!
I want to have this animal!
It's almost time for the show, so we have to get ready.
Ready? Ready?
Link crew!
Yes, we're ready!
Now that we're ready, we're going to go to the show!
I'll be there!